Awesome.
All right, so we're here tonight talking
about how we communicate difficult
topics succinctly. And essentially,
we're trying to see how we can quickly
break down some difficult ideas. So for
today, we're going to ask how can you
break down a difficult experience or
difficult time of yours into about five
words? And you can choose to sort of
narrate how you're choosing those words
or you can just throw them out if you
don't want to give away too much
information, for example.
So feel free to start when you want and
I'll sort of go back and forth with you
as you're navigating.
with it positively.
Sure.
Okay.
It could also be negatively if it
Right.
if we learned something.
good to have both.
Yes.
Besides.
Um
Let's see.
Logic.
Right.
Um let's see.
Uh
Sadness.
Hard time, right?
Um let's see. What's another good one?
Hm.
Remorse.
Ooh, I like that one.
Reasoning.
Mhm.
And then, how many is that so far? Four?
you're at four.
Okay.
Uh
Hm.
Try to try to spitball spitball me one.
Hm?
Cooperation.
There we go.
Hey.
You you you acted out the word. That's
perfect.
the word.